Finding Aid to the Letters to Alfred Stieglitz, 1933-1944, undated MS.9
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Correspondence, 1933-1944, undated; 1
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-1; MS-OKAS-0172; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-2; MS-OKAS-0173; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-3; MS-OKAS-0174; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-4; MS-OKAS-0175; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-5; MS-OKAS-0176; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-7; MS-OKAS-0177; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-8; MS-OKAS-0178; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-9; MS-OKAS-0179; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-10; MS-OKAS-0180; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-10; MS-OKAS-0181; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-12; MS-OKAS-0182; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-14; MS-OKAS-0183; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-15; MS-OKAS-0184; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-16; MS-OKAS-0185; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-17; MS-OKAS-0186; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-18; MS-OKAS-0187; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-19; MS-OKAS-0188; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-21; MS-OKAS-0189; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-22; MS-OKAS-0190; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-24; MS-OKAS-0191; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-25; MS-OKAS-0192; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-26; MS-OKAS-0193; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-28; MS-OKAS-0194; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-29; MS-OKAS-0195; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-31; MS-OKAS-0196; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-8-30; MS-OKAS-0197; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz with enclosed photographs, 1944-8-30; MS-OKAS-0198; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Two photos enclosed of Mr. Chen and Georgia O'Keeffe at the Ghost Ranch house. (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-2; MS-OKAS-0199; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-4; MS-OKAS-0200; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-6; MS-OKAS-0201; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-7; MS-OKAS-0202; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-12; MS-OKAS-0203; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-12; MS-OKAS-0204; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-13; MS-OKAS-0205; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-13; MS-OKAS-0206; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-14; MS-OKAS-0207; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-15; MS-OKAS-0208; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-16; MS-OKAS-0209; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Ansel Adams to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-16; MS-OKAS-0232; Adams, Ansel, 1902-1984; Enclosed article by Alfred Frankenstein, postcard, and pine needles. (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-19; MS-OKAS-0210; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-20; MS-OKAS-0211; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-21; MS-OKAS-0212; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz with enclosed photographs, 1944-9-21; MS-OKAS-0213; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed photographs of Georgia O'Keeffe and friends in New Mexico. (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-22; MS-OKAS-0214; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-23; MS-OKAS-0215; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-25; MS-OKAS-0216; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-27; MS-OKAS-0217; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-28; MS-OKAS-0218; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-9-29; MS-OKAS-0219; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-2; MS-OKAS-0220; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-3; MS-OKAS-0221; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-4; MS-OKAS-0222; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-6; MS-OKAS-0223; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-8; MS-OKAS-0224; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Envelope from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-9; MS-OKAS-0225; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-10; MS-OKAS-0226; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-10; MS-OKAS-0227; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-12; MS-OKAS-0228; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-10-12; MS-OKAS-0229; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 8)
- Photographs, circa 1944; 2
  - Black Place I, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0150e; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; The painting, Black Place I, by Georgia O'Keeffe was photographed sitting upon a chair in the Ghost Ranch patio. The photograph was enclosed in a letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-07-06. (Box 9)
    Photographs
  - Black Place III, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0150f; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; The painting, Black Place III, by Georgia O'Keeffe was photographed sitting upon a chair in the Ghost Ranch patio. The photograph was enclosed in a letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-07-06. (Box 9)
  - Pelvis I, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0150g; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; The painting, Pelvis I, by Georgia O'Keeffe was photographed sitting upon a chair in the Ghost Ranch patio. The photograph was enclosed in a letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-07-06. (Box 9)
  - Mr. Chen and Georgia O'Keeffe at Ghost Ranch, circa 1944; MS-OKAS-0198e; Unknown; Photograph of Mr. Chen and Georgia O'Keeffe at the Ghost Ranch house. Enclosed in a letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-08-30. (Box 9)
  - Mr. Chen and Georgia O'Keeffe at Ghost Ranch, circa 1944; MS-OKAS-0198f; Unknown; Photograph of Mr. Chen and Georgia O'Keeffe at the Ghost Ranch house. Enclosed in a letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-08-30. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Maria Chabot, Max Martinez, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213e; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Maria Chabot, Max Martinez, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213f; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Max Martinez, Bernie Martinez, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213g; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Max Martinez, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213h; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Max Martinez, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213i; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213j; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Climbing Ladder, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213k; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Climbing Ladder, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213l; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, On the Roof, Ghost Ranch House, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213m; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213n; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213o; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213p; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch House Patio, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213q; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe at Ghost Ranch House Window, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213r; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch House Exterior, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213s; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Ghost Ranch House, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213t; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. (Box 9)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe on a Trip to Burns Canyon, 1944; MS-OKAS-0213u; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; Enclosed in a letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz dated 1944-09-22. Burns Canyon is Northwest of Ghost Ranch. (Box 9)